

## **PROFESSIONAL**

Full-stack development
Layout design
Scrum
Angular
C#
Source control management
Issue management systems

### **PERSONAL**

(Jira, Azure)

Creative spirit
Reliable and professional
Time management
Problem-solving
Team player
Collaborating with other
developers
Fast learner
Motivated

## **CONTACT**

+36 30 207 5454 kismarczirobi@gmail.com



in Linkedin

Hungary, szeged

# JOZSEF KISMARCZI

### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

#### **ABOUT**

My name is József Kismarczi and I have been involved in active development since 2018. My skills include the implementation of web design and development principles to create reliable software both on the backend and front-end. I bring mockups to life using a variety of tools, such as HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript (ES6), TypeScript, jQuery and Angular. I am able to communicate technical issues clearly and comprehensibly to the development team. I create responsive and user-friendly products and applications, then monitor their performance and solve problems. I use version control tools like Git to maintain an organized workflow. I have experience in using the .net framework. On the back-end, I also try to comply with SOLID principles, clean code rules and using design patterns to create a WEB API with better performance and more transparent code.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Signal Iduna | 2022 - Now

• Stacks: C#, Angular

**FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER** 

NewLine kft. | 2019 - 2022

- Developing public trasport schedule system websites
- Stacks: C#, Kendo UI, MVC, TypeScript, GIT/TFS, SQL, Web API

#### FRONT END SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Pc Trade Systems kft. | Jun 2018 - Dec 2018

• Angular, Scrum, Jira ticket management

#### **EDUCATION**

FLOW ACADEMY - Software developer | 2018